Guide to the Floyd Millard Riddick Papers, 1909-2000
Floyd Millard Riddick papers 1909-2000
- Accession (2008-0179) 1933-1992
  - Publications, 1978-1993 (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
  - Clippings (Box Acc. 07/165: Box 1)
  - Academics, 1933-1955
  - Correspondence, 1977-1992
  - Miscellaneous drafts and photocopies
  - Senate Resolution 443
- Accession (2014-0073) 1937-2007
  The addition (2014-0073) (140 items; 0.2 lin. ft; 1937-2007) contains publications, biographical materials, clippings, correspondence, two print materials, photographs, and several miscellaneous drafs and documents. Publications include Riddick's descriptions of general Senate procedures and protocol,including those during impeachment. The bulk of the photographs, correspondence, and clippings are from the end of Riddick's life (1980-2000).
  - Biographical publications, 1966-2000 and undated (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - Clippings (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - Correspondence, 1938-2007 and undated (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - "Founders of the Cosmos Club" (1966 print) (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - Miscellaneous documents (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - Miscellaneous drafts (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - Photographs (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - "Point of Opinion" (2004 print) (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)
  - Publications, 1937-1985 (Box Acc. 14/73: 1)